I eat an entire pint of ice cream every
single night and still maintain a
caloric deficit. Here are some of the
recipes I made this week to stay fit and
hit my protein goal. Started off the
week by recreating Dairy Queen's brownie
batter Blizzard. This was a brownie
batter base with brownie pieces mixed
in. Then I had to do another Dairy Queen
recreation. This was the snow drift
blizzard, which was a blue cake batter
base with Oreos and a marshmallow swirl.
A couple weeks ago, one of my followers
challenged me to recreate Ben & Jerry's
Chocolotted Cheesecake Sundae. And so I
did it because I'm never gonna say no to
a challenge. And Bro might have been on
to something because this was busting.
Then I decided to start a new series on
the channel where I recreate viral
I see on my feed and turn into protein
ice cream. This was the blank street
banana bread matcha. So it had banana
matcha and then all of those banana
bread spices. I also had to recreate the
Ben & Jerry's salted caramel almond
flavor because you guys seem to love the
Ben & Jerry's recreations. This recipe
will be out in a couple days, so follow
along and stay tuned for that. Then I
dipped into the Ben & Jerry's flavor
graveyard to pull out the red velvet
cake. This blew up because you guys
thought it looked like me. Not going to
disagree or agree, but I know it tasted
phenomenal. And then I ended off the
week with yet another Ben & Jerry's
recreation. This was Minter Wonderland,
which was a dark chocolate peppermint
base with Oreos and a marshmallow swirl.